{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Tile Flooring Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40038/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40038,"taskName":"Tile: Ceramic and Porcelain - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Ceramic or Porcelain Tile","xmTaskDescriptor":"Tile Flooring Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":390,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"ceramic marble counter slate quartz","textMessagingName":"Repair Ceramic Tile","rolloverLongDesc":"Repair, partially replace or extend existing tile work.","rolloverShortDesc":"Repairs or alterations to existing tile work.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Ceramic or Porcelain Tile.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Ceramic Tile Flooring Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Repair Porcelain Floor Tiles","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":74,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Ceramic \u0026 Porcelain Tile Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Tile: Ceramic and Porcelain - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Ceramic and Porcelain Tile Project","urlName":"Tile-Ceramic-and-Porcelain-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Ceramic \u0026 Porcelain Tile Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"ceramic,marble,counter,slate,quartz,mosaic,porcelain,tiles,installer,flooring,tile,vanities,mantel,vanity,hearth,floor,mosaic, countertops","emcCategoryOid":-12073,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":362,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40038/":{"taskOID":40038,"originalTaskOID":40038,"setID":362,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5115,"questionDisplayText":"Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the damage? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1689,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cracked","answerDisplayText":"Cracked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5501,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Scratched","answerDisplayText":"Scratched","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1383,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chipped","answerDisplayText":"Chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3658,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Loose","answerDisplayText":"Loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7121,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Worn","answerDisplayText":"Worn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6357,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tile discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Tile discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2875,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Grout has mold/mildew","answerDisplayText":"Grout has mold/mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2873,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Grout discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Grout discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2872,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Grout damaged or gone","answerDisplayText":"Grout damaged or gone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2878,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Grout needs cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Grout needs cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2880,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Grout needs sealing","answerDisplayText":"Grout needs sealing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6806,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Want to change grout color","answerDisplayText":"Want to change grout color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4048,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Need caulking","answerDisplayText":"Need caulking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5118,"questionDisplayText":"Tile Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the tile located? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":930,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6533,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tub/shower stall","answerDisplayText":"Tub/shower stall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6220,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Swimming Pool","answerDisplayText":"Swimming Pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5488,"questionDisplayText":"Spare Tiles","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you have spare tiles left over from installation?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5115,"questionDisplayText":"Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the damage? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1689,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cracked","answerDisplayText":"Cracked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5501,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Scratched","answerDisplayText":"Scratched","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1383,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chipped","answerDisplayText":"Chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3658,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Loose","answerDisplayText":"Loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7121,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Worn","answerDisplayText":"Worn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6357,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tile discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Tile discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2875,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Grout has mold/mildew","answerDisplayText":"Grout has mold/mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2873,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Grout discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Grout discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2872,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Grout damaged or gone","answerDisplayText":"Grout damaged or gone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2878,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Grout needs cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Grout needs cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2880,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Grout needs sealing","answerDisplayText":"Grout needs sealing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6806,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Want to change grout color","answerDisplayText":"Want to change grout color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4048,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Need caulking","answerDisplayText":"Need caulking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1689,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cracked","answerDisplayText":"Cracked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5501,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Scratched","answerDisplayText":"Scratched","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1383,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chipped","answerDisplayText":"Chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3658,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Loose","answerDisplayText":"Loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7121,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Worn","answerDisplayText":"Worn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6357,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tile discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Tile discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2875,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Grout has mold/mildew","answerDisplayText":"Grout has mold/mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2873,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Grout discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Grout discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2872,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Grout damaged or gone","answerDisplayText":"Grout damaged or gone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2878,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Grout needs cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Grout needs cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2880,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Grout needs sealing","answerDisplayText":"Grout needs sealing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6806,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Want to change grout color","answerDisplayText":"Want to change grout color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4048,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Need caulking","answerDisplayText":"Need caulking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5118,"questionDisplayText":"Tile Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the tile located? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":930,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6533,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tub/shower stall","answerDisplayText":"Tub/shower stall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6220,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Swimming Pool","answerDisplayText":"Swimming Pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":930,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6533,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tub/shower stall","answerDisplayText":"Tub/shower stall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6220,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Swimming Pool","answerDisplayText":"Swimming Pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5488,"questionDisplayText":"Spare Tiles","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you have spare tiles left over from installation?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}